smartmobilephonesolutions.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Smart Mobile Phone Solutions

The following information is to help users and visitors (collectively “Users” or “You”) understand how Smart Mobile Phone Solutions (“SMPS,” “We,” “Us,”) collects, uses, disseminates and safeguards the information You provide to us while accessing and using our website or service (collectively, the “Services”), and any other websites and services as may be added from time to time (collectively, the “Service”). We will not use or share Your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. By using the Smart Mobile Phone Solutions Services, you expressly consent to the practices and activities described in this document.

#### **User Provided Information**

We may collect and store certain PII (personally identifiable information) that You provide personally to Us directly, such as Your first and last name, telephone number, address, credit card or PayPal® information, and email address (collectively, “Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”) when choosing to register, to participate in promotions or surveys, to subscribe to any newsletters or other distribution lists, or to enter into or participate in contests, drawings, raffles, or sweepstakes. You may also choose to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information in your User Content.

#### **Cookies**

Android isn’t the only thing that likes desserts. Instead of Cupcakes, Donuts, Éclairs, Froyos, Gingerbread, Ice Cream Sandwiches, or Jelly Beans, We use Cookies! When you use our Services We may send one or more cookies to your computer. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. These Cookies can be used for multiple reasons including helping Us identify your web browser.

Like virtual keys, cookies unlock a computer's memory and allow our Services to recognize Users when they return to the site. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems. They are merely text files that can be deleted at any time - they are not plug-ins nor are they programs. Cookies cannot be used to spread viruses and they cannot access your hard drive. Like a key, a cookie itself does not contain information, but when it is read by a browser it can help Us improve the Services delivered.

For more information about these types of cookies you can perform a web search for “HTTP cookie” on your favorite search engine.

#### **Log Files**

Log file information is automatically reported by your web browser each time You view a web page. When You register with or use the Services, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever You visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your IP address, browser type and language, number of clicks, domain names of websites visited, pages viewed, and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time.

#### **Clear Gifs**

When You use the Services, We may use clear gifs (a.k.a. web beacons, or web bugs) which are pieces of data used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously. In addition, We may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make Smart Mobile Phone Solutions better for our Users.

Information collected through clear gifs, cookies and log file information is largely non-personally identifiable information because such information is not collected or used in such a way that an individual User can be identified, for example, by name or email address (collectively, “Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). Collected information may be Personally Identifiable Information or Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

#### **Third-party service-based information**

Third-party supported services, such as Google Analytics, that You might use on the Services may collect information through similar methods. Such information is not shared with us and is subject to the privacy policy of each such third-party service.

#### **Use of Information**

We may use collected information to:

( **a** ) Remember information so that You will not have to re-enter it during your current or subsequent visits to the Services; ( **b** ) Access your information after You sign in; ( **c** ) Provide custom, personalized content and information; ( **d** ) Monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; ( **e** ) Monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; ( **f** ) Track User Content, and status in any promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; ( **g** ) Market our Service to advertisers and other third parties; ( **h** ) Diagnose or fix technology problems; ( **i** ) Verify your identity for payment and taxation purposes; ( **j** ) To improve the quality and design of the Services and to create new features by storing, tracking, and analyzing your preferences and trends.

#### **User Submissions**

Any information or User Content submitted, transmitted, or uploaded to the public areas of the Service becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by other Users, who may forward this information or User Content to other websites or people.

Be aware that if Your User Content or if Your Submitted Content includes personal information, such as your name and email address, other Users will have access to it. If Your User Content is or includes a photograph, please be aware that all photographs uploaded to the Services reside on public URLs. Any person who knows the URL of Your photograph can access the photograph, whether or not it’s published. Your photograph might remain displayed on such URL even after You delete it from Your Submitted Content. Please do not upload any photographs that You do not want to be public information.

For more information about User Submissions see our Terms of Use.

#### **Third-Party Service Providers**

Services may be used in conjunction with services provided through a variety of third parties, such as Google. The use of User Content and other information provided by You to such third parties is governed by their privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or their compliance with such policies.

We may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements and/or collect information on or threw our Services. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on SMPS. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Us to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements of interest to You. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.

#### **Merger or Acquisition**

In the event that we acquire, are acquired by, or merge with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign all collected information as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

#### **Changes and Updates**

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any current revisions.
